

MY BACKGROUND

Birth date 19.08.1996 (23 y.o)

I am a computer science graduate and an experienced programmer, web developer with main stack based on JS.

SPECIALIZATIONS

- Javascript 8/10
- Vue JS 7/10
- Nuxt JS 5/10
- · Webpack 5/10
- · Node/Express JS 4/10
- Jquery 9/10
- React JS 3/10
- HTML/CSS 9/10
- · Wordpress 7/10
- PHP 3/10

CORE COMPETENCIES

- · Front-end coding
- · Back-end coding
- Databases
- · Full Stack Web Development
- Flexbox layout
- Adaptive layout

LANGUAGES

- English- 7/10
- · Russian, Ukrainian 10/10

ALEXANDER SHATRAVKA

Web Developer • JS Developer

CONTACT INFORMATION

Kharkov, Ukraine +380955838911

Telegram: @alexander_shatravka

E-mail: alexander.shatravka@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-shatravka-b04338151/

CAREER SUMMARY

Web Developer, JS Developer

TSN-Media

August 2019 - May 2020

Worked as multi-platform frontend developer and full-stack web developer. JS, Vue JS, JQuery, on front. PHP, Node js on back end part of applications

Frontend, Web Developer

Fedorov Band Consulting (Viral digital agency)

October 2018 - August 2019

Worked as a full-stack web developer with projects which includes JS functionality, online stores, wordpress project, web-application for small business with backend implemented with php and Telegram API.

Frontend, Web Developer

CashYou

April 2018 - October 2018

Developed and maintained Web application for online credits on Symfony PHP.

Frontend developer

(Freelance)

December 2017 - March 2018 Markup development

EDUCATION

National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute", Kharkiv, Ukraine – Master degree, 2019

Faculty: Computer information technologies.

Courses:

- Summer 2019 Fullstack JS development Nure IT academy,
- Winter 2017 Sun Rise English course (B2 level)
- Summer 2017 Epam external course Front-end development.